freepressindex.com 2013-04-21

# Privacy Policy - FreePressIndex.com

Updated on October 24, 2007 

Below is the Privacy Policy for Freepressindex.com, please read this carefully. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to address new issues and reflect changes on our sites, and as the need arises. All changes to this privacy policy will be posted here, please read this privacy policy every time you visit Freepressindex. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please send us an e-mail at **info@freepressindex.com**

**Sharing Of Information:**  
We do not share users information with third parties. The only time information is shared when a user of Freepressindex.com submits their contact information during distribution of their press release. 

**Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Free Advantages:**  
If you want to remain completely anonymous, you're still free to take advantage of the wealth of content available on our site.

**Information Collection and usage:**  
Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site.

**Web Links Responsibility:**   
Our site includes links to other websites, and provides access to products and services offered by third parties but we are do not take any responsiblity or liability of these sites.

**Cookies:**  
A "cookie" is a small data file that can be stored on your hard drive when you browse certain Web sites. FreePressIndex only uses cookies to gather information for statistical analysis to improve website services in order to provide more customer satisfaction. These cookies are not used to provide information to any third party. 

You may choose to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser setting. A cookie does not give access to your computer or any data relevant to you, other than the information you choose to share with us.

**Log Files:**  
We log, access times, browser types and URLs. We do not sell or give out this information to any third parties. This information is not personally identifiable information, and it is used for statistical purposes only. 

Thank you for reviewing our privacy policy!
